Guide to the Stanford Museum Collection
Stanford University Library
- Museum objects
  - Memorabilia from Farewell dinner to General Porfirio Diaz on his departure from New York, Union League Club, 24 April 1883 - notice of dinner and guest list (includes Hon. Leland Stanford) printed on silk, with fringed edges. Notice has painted vignettes., ARCH-AM-2004-017 (Box 1)
  - Memorabilia from Muir and Burbank houses: sweatshirt with image of Sterling on back and "faculty associate" on front, awarded to graduating senior 1959; 3 mugs with image of Bufano's "Penguin" statue that used to sit between Muir and Burbank houses. See collection file for further notes, ARCH-AM-2002-32 (Box 1)
    2002-32.1 Sweatshirt 2002-32.2 Mug 2002-32.3 Mug 2002-32.4 Mug
  - Memorabilia from presidential inauguration of Benjamin Harrison 1889, ARCH-AM-2005-002 (Box 1)
    2005-002.1 Inaugural ball program 2005-002.2 Inaugural ball program 2005-002.3 Souvenir menu 2005-002.4 image of B. Harrison on unknown surface 2005-002.5 image of Mrs. Harrison on unknown surface
  - Memorabilia: Buttons, reunion ID tags, Class of '51 address stamps, red feather, paper flag of Mexico, ARCH-AM-2007-021 (Box 1)
    2007-021.1 Button: Once an Indian Always an Indian 2007-021.2 Button: red S 2007-021.3 Button: red S with laurel leaves on either side 2007-021.4 Button: Stanford '51 2007-021.5 Button: Stanford '51 with ribbons 2007-021.6 Button: Stanford 1951-2001 with 51 in square inside diamond 2007-021.7 Button: I'm Excited! 2007-021.8 Button (rectangle): COMMITTEE 2007-021.9 Red feather 2007-021.10 Class of '51 address stamps (Bowman House) - 2 items 2007-021.11 Reunion ID for Joe Cusick 2001 2007-021.12 Reunion ID for Kathy Cusick 2001 2007-021.13 Reunion ID for Joe Cusick 2006 (with 2 pins) 2007-021.14 Paper flag of Mexico 2007-021.15 Reunion ID for Joe Cusick 1996 2007-021.16 Reunion ID for Joe Cusick (35th) 1986 2007-021.17 Reunion (25th) Committee ribbons
  - Memorabilia: leather bookmark [triangular with U seal] and wooden box for Wilson's chocolates [Wilson's Choclat Chunks. The Candy with a College Education. with image of front of Quad], ARCH-AM-2008-009 (Box 1)
    2008-009.1 leather bookmark 2008-009.2 Wilson's wooden box
  - memorabilia: t-shirts, banners, sign, ARCH-AM-1985-09 (Box 1)
    1. T-shirt: "Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week. GLAS of Stanford 1985": purple, sleeveless 2. T-shirt: "Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week. GLAS of Stanford 1985": purple, sleeveless 3. T-shirt: "Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week. GLAS of Stanford 1985": maroon 4. Banner: "Dykes Fix Stanford" (Hoover Tower Protest Rally, 1983) 5. Banner: "Gay and Lesbian Awareness Week", ca. 1985 6. Banner: Northern California Gay and Lesbian Students (black with rainbow colors), 1984 7. Sign: "Enter from the Rear" (black and white lettering)
  - Memorial Metal Pillow. 19X23X38 cm. In case. To Mrs. Stanford from locomotive engineers. In memory of Leland Sr., ARCH-AM-2000-186 (Box 1)
  - Menu from the dinner given by Mrs. Leland Stanford in Honolulu to resident graduates of LSJU, April 28, 1902 - printed on red silk (3 items), ARCH-AM-2004-021 (Box 1)
  - Menu printed on silk from dinner at Union League Club, April 21, 1883. Menu is on larger banner with 'Hon. Leland Stanford" written on botton portion, ARCH-AM-2004-019 (Box 1)
  - Messonier oil studies (3), ARCH-AM-1981-09 (Box 1)
  - metal and procelain wreaths from the Mausoleum, ARCH-AM-1998-013 (Box 1)
    013.1 cross with flowers (smaller) 013.2 cross with flowers (larger) 013.3 round wreath with flowers 013.4 oval wreath, leaves only 013.5 wooden cross, no flowers or decoration; envelope with loose pieces
  - Metal Cable, 1" section (copper), ARCH-AM-1985-10 (Box 1)
  - Metal cup, 8.4 cm high, "Souvenir of Stanford University" with images of outer quadrangle, Memorial Church, Memorial Arch, quadrangle from arcade, Palo Alto tree. On underside: made in Germany for H. W. Simkins, Palo Alto, Calif., ARCH-AM-1999-016 (Box 1)
  - Metal lath for plaster walls in Main Quad and assumed original light fixture taken from arcade, ARCH-AM-2005-033 (Box 1)
  - metal mold for making glass globes used in Quad Arcades, ARCH-AM-2000-040 (Box 1)
  - Metal mold used to produce glass shades for replica lamps in Bldg. 30 (replica of 1890's lights used in quad bldgs). Very heavy item, ARCH-AM-1997-002 (Box 1)
  - Metal part for the Albion printing press, ca. 1860; ARCH-AM-2009-037 (Box 1)
  - Metal plaque mounted on wooden shield, 41X42 cm. Stanford shield., ARCH-AM-2000-149 (Box 1)
  - metal plaque of the Stanford Flying Club [exact usage unknown]: university seal (with German motto) with Flying Club logo over the tree, ARCH-AM-2002-38 (Box 1)
  - Metal plaque: Dohrmann Grove / In Memory of Emilie Elizabeth Dohrmann / 1879-1966, ARCH-AM-2001-21 (Box 1)
  - Metal plaque: univ. seal (Die Luft) made to be mounted (on wall?), ARCH-AM-1980-14 (Box 1)
  - metal sign, red, with STANFORD in white letters and L'il Injun head, ARCH-AM-2000-002 (Box 1)
  - Metal Sign: "David Starr Jordan reading address. Dedication of SU, Oct. 1 1891.", ARCH-AM-2000-158 (Box 1)
  - Metal Sign. 18X5 cm. "Martin Kellogg, Pres. State University reading address. Dedication of SU, Oct. 1 1891.", ARCH-AM-2000-156 (Box 1)
  - Metal Sign. 5X20 cm. "Judge James M. McShafter reading address, Dedication of SU, Oct. 1 1891.", ARCH-AM-2000-157 (Box 1)
  - Metal tools (3) used in constructing Quad balusters 2002 (or 2001?), ARCH-AM-2002-29 (Box 1)
    Box 1 contains 2 tools (rectangular ones); Box 2 contains 1 tool (curved edge one)
  - Metal version of seal (presidential?) used in commencement activities; made by company that did new commencement stage (2000), ARCH-AM-2000-023 (Box 1)
  - Model of demolished Encina Gym, ca. 2003 (includes Bakewell Building which was not demolished), ARCH-AM-2005-032 (Box 1)
  - Monogramed silver coffee pot (8.75" tall) and tray (14" diameter). Both have stamp on bottom of "G M Co" with symbol of an anchor in a shield, ARCH-AM-1998-014 (Box 1)
    98-014.1 coffee pot 98-014.2 tray
  - Mortar boards (1 black, 1 grey) with note, circa 1894; ARCH-AM-2000-057 (Box 1)
    Grey mortar board Black mortar board; initials E.B.M. on inside of cap
  - Mosaic chunks from Memorial Church, 1906 Printing plates for Memorial Church, ARCH-AM-1991-098 (Box 1)
  - Mosaic piece from rubble of Memorial Church after the 1906 earthquake - half in blue pieces; other half is part of a red circle with green interior and gold background [6.5 in. point to point], ARCH-AM-2005-042 (Box 1)
  - Mosaic piece, from Memorial Church, after 1906 earthquake damage [8 x 6 in.; design includes gold half-circle with blue interior from which lines of blue, gold, red and green pieces radiate; below the half-circle are red, white, and brown pieces], ARCH-AM-2000-046 (Box 1)
  - Mosaic piece, from Memorial Church, after 1906 earthquake damage. 10 x 21.5 inches, ARCH-AM-2000-045 (Box 1)
  - Mosaic; Piece from Memorial Church, gold bkg. 25x53x2 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-316 (Box 1)
  - Mounted poster - Barry Goldwater for President. 3.5 x 4.5 ft., ARCH-AM-1997-017 (Box 1)
  - nail taken from Bldg 1 in the Quad when the entry way was remodeled (ca. 1975). Nail is square and 2.5 inches long; note by Royden included., ARCH-AM-1998-010 (Box 1)
  - nail, old, iron 4 X 2 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-144 (Box 1)
  - Nail: old iron, 15 X 2 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-143 (Box 1)
  - Name plate for Henry J. Adams Jr. '30. Found on back of a junked chair, in the 1960s., ARCH-AM-2003-013 (Box 1)
  - Name tags, class of '62 reunion. white with red logo., ARCH-AM-1984-39 (Box 1)
  - Napkin, "Stanford 1891-1941": occasion unknown, ARCH-AM-1994-14 (Box 1)
  - New Student Orientation button: "Welcome! Stanford 2000", ARCH-AM-2000-024 (Box 1)
    5 copies of one button
  - Number skipped. No item with this number., ARCH-AM-2000-130.09 (Box 1)
  - Object of wood, 25cm long, fish hads(?) carved on bottom (DSJ related?), ARCH-AM-2000-147 (Box 1)
  - Oil colored photographs of Memorial Church interior; Bear Photo No. 904 and 910, framed [image post-1906 but items bears no date], ARCH-AM-2005-045 (Box 1)
    2005-045.1 No. 910 Interior of Church 2005-045.2 No. 904 Facade of Church thru arcade arch
  - Oil painting (20x26 in.) possibly of child; very dirty and stained, ARCH-AM-2008-016 (Box 1)
  - Oil painting of Felix Bloch by Daniel Mendelowitz (framed), 1946; ARCH-AM-2010-002 (Box 1)
  - Oil painting of Wilred H. Stone by Daniel Mendelowitz, 1963; framed. See collection file for more information on creation of the painting., ARCH-AM-2000-035 (Box 1)
  - oil painting on canvas, probably of Mary Yost (n.d.) 16 x 21 inches; unframed, ARCH-AM-1998-009 (Box 1)
  - Oil painting, sailing ship, painted by Leland Jr., ARCH-AM-2000-072 (Box 1)
  - Oil Painting, Stanford's Residences east and west. 29x46 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-100 (Box 1)
  - Oil Painting: 53x67 cm. of man with mustache, Artist's initials; B.H.W.,S/F/gold frame; 91x79 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-077 (Box 1)
  - Oil Painting: 66x53, portrait of woman signed; Duesbury Wolfe, gold frame - 91x79 cm, ARCH-AM-2000-076 (Box 1)
  - Oil portrait of J. E. W. Sterling, ARCH-AM-2004-007 (Box 1)
  - Oil Portrait, Thomas S. Barclay., ARCH-AM-2000-334 (Box 1)
  - Oil sketch for final presidential portrait of R. W. Lyman, ARCH-AM-2003-007 (Box 1)
  - Oil Sketch, Jordon, David Starr by Xavier Martinez 1917. o.d. 53x46 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-079 (Box 1)
  - On the President's Review of the War-Fleets peacefully anchored in New York Harbour, April 27th, 1893 - poem by Patrick M. King, printed on silk, ARCH-AM-2004-018 (Box 1)
  - One of original 12 Board of Trustees chairs - wooden, high back, leather upholstered., ARCH-AM-1997-015 (Box 1)
  - One pair of plaster hands, casted, of David Starr Jordan, ARCH-AM-2000-001 (Box 1)
  - One pin, one ring, and miniature mallet, ARCH-AM-2000-041 (Box 1)
    041.1 broken rifle pin 041.2 ring with hand in peace sign (damaged) 041.3 miniature mallet
  - Opera glasses holder (?), ARCH-AM-1992-07 (Box 1)
  - Order of the Baluster presented to Jim Triolo July 2, 1960 [An original stair baluster from Encina with 4 text plaques attached, one of which lists his colleagues - Lyle Cook, Ken Cuthbertson, Dave Jacobxon, Daryl Pearson, Joe Ruetz and others], ARCH-AM-2006-025 (Box 1)
  - Orientation buttons (6 copies) - "Welcome! 2001 Stanford Orientation", ARCH-AM-2001-19 (Box 1)
  - Orientation buttons 2007 [no date on button]: I [heart] Freshmen; I [heart] Transfers; and I [heart] Freshmen Transfers (7 buttons in all), ARCH-AM-2008-005 (Box 1)
  - Orientation buttons, 1995, 1996, 1997, 1998, ARCH-AM-1998-016 (Box 1)
    016.1 "Welcome" 1995 016.2 "Stanford Welcomes You!" 1996 016.3 "Welcome! Stanford Orientation 1997" 016.4 "Welcome! Stanford Orientation 1997" 016.5 "Welcome! Stanford Orientation 1997" 016.6 "Welcome to STANFORD! 1998 Orientation" 016.7 "Welcome to STANFORD! 1998 Orientation" 016.8 "Welcome to STANFORD! 1998 Orientation"
  - Orientation gift box labeled "good stuff The Student Sampler" with "female" in the lower right corner - contained toiletries, laundry soap, etc. (1977), ARCH-AM-2001-16 (Box 1)
  - Original bindings for 2 volumes of the Jane L. Stanford letters [letters removed 1998], no date; ARCH-AM-2009-009 (Box 1)
  - Original copper box used for the time capsule buried in building 160 in 1898., ARCH-AM-2002-27 (Box 1)
  - Original gas valve from boiler at Meyer Buck estate (failed and removed in 1982), ARCH-AM-1997-025 (Box 1)
  - Original linoleum flooring in dorm rooms, Toyon Hall, ARCH-AM-2002-03 (Box 1)
  - Original mortar from Quad balusters and balustrade (no date given), undated; ARCH-AM-2009-023 (Box 1)
    1 envelope of mortar pieces
  - Original stair balusters from Encina (blown out by the fire-hose prank) that were used as "Order of the Baluster" awards to fund-raisers, ARCH-AM-2001-35 (Box 1)
    35.1 awarded to Charles W. Getchell, Jr., 1959 Stanford Fund 35.2 awarded to Charles W. Getchell, Jr., 1961 Stanford Fund 35.3 awarded to Joseph D. Cusick, 1963/64 Stanford Fund 35.4 awarded to Joseph D. Cusick, 1964/65 Stanford Fund
  - Original Stanford colors, framed., ARCH-AM-2000-351 (Box 1)
  - Originally: Assorted items (hats, cans, papers) found under the Drell House and others that were moved in the Spring of 2006 (to make way for the Munger dorms), ARCH-AM-2006-015 (Box 1)
    Items retained: 2 wooden hangers from PA cleaners; bills, checks, and photos of Daniel Drell; Ruth Sterne's German I test; 2 letters and 1 card
  - Ornate Gold Frame, o.d. 96x86 cm., red velvet mount (no picture), ARCH-AM-2000-087 (Box 1)
  - OS reproductions of images of the frieze from the Memorial Arch used in a mock-up of the Arch created in the Art Dept. (5 boards), ARCH-AM-2006-011 (Box 1)
  - OSOC tshirt ("Who runs Stanford?" "WE DO! OSOC" and buttons, red letters on white: O S O C, ARCH-AM-1981-13 (Box 1)
    81-13.1 tshirt 81-13.2 Lapel button (5)
  - Oxford Hood and mortor board of Dr. Charles Gardner, chaplain, ARCH-AM-1983-10 (Box 1)
  - Paddle board, ARCH-AM-2000-031 (Box 1)
  - Paddleboard, F. E. Terman's "F.E. Turman, TC 9" carved in it. 10 x 56 x 2 cm., ARCH-AM-1984-55 (Box 1)
  - Paint samples from various external and internal walls of The Knoll, ARCH-AM-2005-039 (Box 1)
  - painting of DS Jordan by R. C. Medel (3/21/47) on a large shell with bamboo holder, ARCH-AM-1993-15 (Box 1)
  - Painting on glass of library with Hoover Tower in background, ARCH-AM-1991-108 (Box 1)
  - Painting, framed, glass, Horse by E. Wythen Back. v. 1870. frame 72x87 cm, image 42x55 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-286 (Box 1)
  - Painting, Oil in frame (no glass) 38X29cm. To jane from Mrs. Stanford, a scene., ARCH-AM-2000-179 (Box 1)
  - Painting, watercolor, the chimney in Engineering Grounds, pre-1906, from site of old camp, by Mrs. J.O. Griffin. frame 47x33, image 31x21.[MOVED TO PRINT COLLECTION 2/2006], ARCH-AM-2000-274 (Box 1)
  - Painting; watercolor, framed, glass. Oak Tree. frame 28x23, image 16x23 cm. [MOVED TO PRINT COLLECTION 2/2006], ARCH-AM-2000-298 (Box 1)
  - Paintings on wood by E. Messonier, ARCH-AM-1985-01 (Box 1)
    85-01.1 framed, glass, man; dog; hands with guns 85-01.2 Framed, calss, foot soldier 85-01.3 framed, glass, Head of Horse
  - Pair of flip-flops: red with STANFORD '78 on straps and with tree holding the axe on bottom, ARCH-AM-2005-017 (Box 1)
  - Pants, Football (?). 74X36 cm. White canvas with red canvas belt. Padded partially over hips and at knees., ARCH-AM-2000-132 (Box 1)
  - Pants, Football(?) 81X40 cm. Brown, khaki, padded, soiled, and torn., ARCH-AM-2000-134 (Box 1)
  - Pants, Football(?) 76X38cm. Heavily padded, patched and soiled., ARCH-AM-2000-135 (Box 1)
  - Paper fan from "Lizzie Borden on Trial" - event held during installation of Barbara Babcock as Crown Professor, Law School, 9/16/97., ARCH-AM-1997-018 (Box 1)
  - Paper fan from 115th convocation [2005] with program and text for Hail, Stanford, Hail on reverse, ARCH-AM-2009-001 (Box 1)
  - Paper visors used at the 1984 commencement at Sunken Diamond, "I survived the Sunken Diamond" (7), ARCH-AM-1984-14 (Box 1)
  - Patterns (7) for the medallions on the Stanford Family Statue. [Round patterns about 10" diameter mounted on wooden boards, 14 x 23 inches.], ARCH-AM-2001-22 (Box 1)
  - Pencil and Ink Sketch by Leland Jr., 30x51 cm.; wood frame - o.d. 53x74 cm. "Christmas Gift to my dear Mama from Leland",) ct 25, 1875., ARCH-AM-2000-083 (Box 1)
  - Pennant, 14 3/4" long; red felt w/ white printed letters "Stanford" and LSJU seal; white trim at wide end., ARCH-AM-1982-07 (Box 1)
  - Pennant, with letter of explanation, ARCH-AM-2000-040 (Box 1)
  - Pennant. 12x30". Red, with white lettering. "Stanford" cartoon, Indian Holding stadium, ARCH-AM-1984-01 (Box 1)
  - Pennants, armband, and silk letter S, ARCH-AM-2007-024 (Box 1)
    2007-024.1 Red felt pennant, STANFORD in white felt 2007-024.2 Red felt pennant, with Indian head and STANFORD in white 2007-024.3 Red felt armband with S in white felt 2007-024.4 scrap of red silk with white S in center
  - Personal mementoes of Harris J. Ryan, 1887-1927; ARCH-AM-2010-006 (Box 1)
    2010-006.1 Thomas Alva Edison Award from the American Institute of Electrical Engineers 1925 2010-006.2 Engineers Club San Francisco Honorary Member [silver?] club card with case made from ostrich skin 1927 2010-006.3 Badge of the American Institute of Electrical Engineers (first one adopted) ca. 1890 2010-006.4 Engineering tool with case 2010-006.5 Engineering tool with case 2010-006.6 Badge: Judge Columbian Exhibition 1893 2010-006.7 AIEE badge: on reverse President 1923-1924 2010-006.8 Tiffany case holding 3 badges (pins) from fraternal organizations
  - Pewter Mug inscribed with several names (1907-1939): possibly football item, ARCH-AM-1991-093 (Box 1)
  - PhD acad. hood - Earth Sciences: blue velvet with terra cotta satin lining, ARCH-AM-1995-29 (Box 1)
  - Photgraph, Framed. 55X48 cm. BW photo of Leland Stanford, Jr. Red velved mat, elaborate gold frame. Photo: 15X10 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-161 (Box 1)
  - Photo collage and crew patch from fight of the Space Shuttle Discovery, May 27-June 6, 1999. Ellen Ochoa (Ph.D. 1985) was in the crew. Includes image of Ochoa with Stanford pennant., ARCH-AM-2000-039 (Box 1)
  - Photo frame (art nouveau) metal; with photo of Jesse Thomson, '06, ARCH-AM-1980-23 (Box 1)
  - Photo of five S. U. golf team members from GOLF DIGEST 1995 - laminated on board, ARCH-AM-1996-13 (Box 1)
  - Photo portraits of Leland Stanford, Leland Stanford Jr., and Jane (from trip to Japan) in elaborate frames behind glass. Intended for a "Stanford Room" at the clinic. All appear to be original prints, not copy prints., ARCH-AM-2001-14 (Box 1)
    2001-14.1 Leland Stanford [small portion of the gold interior frame has broken off] 2001-14.2 Leland Stanford, Jr. 2001-14.3 Jane Stanford in Japan
  - Photo- front view Quad, c. 1905., ARCH-AM-2000-356 (Box 1)
  - Photo, framed. Govenors Lane., ARCH-AM-2000-355 (Box 1)
  - Photo; Leland Stanford, Jr. 14X9 cm image, 18X13 cm frame, gold. BW image. With cane and derby., ARCH-AM-2000-122 (Box 1)
  - Photo; Leland Stanford, Jr. 13X19 cm image 18X13cm. Frame. Image on ceramic curved surface. Gold frame., ARCH-AM-2000-120 (Box 1)
  - Photogragh, Leland Stanford, Jr. 188(?). 18x8 cm. BW of L.S. Jr., arms folded on wicker bench, elaborate gold frame., ARCH-AM-2000-116 (Box 1)
  - Photograph (Unframed) Oval, 36X28 cm. Leland Stanford, Sr. BW, ARCH-AM-2000-177 (Box 1)
  - Photograph [actually a pen ink drawing on watercolor paper]; framed, glass, BW; Front View Memorial Church, signed Fermin Rocker. frame 52x53 cm, image 31x46 cm. UNFRAMED, NOW CLASSED AS PRINT 305, ARCH-AM-2000-284 (Box 1)
  - Photograph and Map, framed, glass. Palo Alto and town of LS Jr. Univ. old scenes of quad/ frame 124x95cm, image 97x67cm., ARCH-AM-2000-331 (Box 1)
  - Photograph by Berton Crandall; framed, glass, BW; front oblique view of Quad, pre 1906. frame 30x35 cm, image 23x34 cm. [REMOVED 2/2006], ARCH-AM-2000-294 (Box 1)
  - Photograph of man on wooden stretcher, BW; 51X45 cm., c.1900, ARCH-AM-2000-181 (Box 1)
  - Photograph of two women. 20X11 cm frame. Oval, gold, opens up. BW on each side. Outside has black with white flowers., ARCH-AM-2000-126 (Box 1)
  - Photograph on cloth, mounted on wood of Pres. Benjamin Harrison. Photo 15x10cm, mount = 27x19x2cm, ARCH-AM-2000-207 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, framed, glass. Leland Stanford Sr. Signed Bradley Ruiatson. frame 103x92, image78x67. (while Gov. of Ca.), ARCH-AM-2000-320 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, Aerial View of Stanford, 135x86 cm. BW mounted on cardboard., ARCH-AM-2000-102 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, Aerial view of Stanford, 24x68 cm., BW mounted on masonite., ARCH-AM-2000-103 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, Aerial view of Stanford, 66x76 cm. BW mounted on Masonite., ARCH-AM-2000-104 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, BW, ARCH-AM-2000-168 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, BW; Leland Stanford Jr. (c hat cane; 27x38 cm. in gold frame (81x69 cm.), ARCH-AM-2000-075 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, BW, framed, J.K.J. (Jessie Jordan) about 20 years of age. frame 35x26cm, image 33x24cm. [REMOVED 2/2006], ARCH-AM-2000-275 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, by Habenicht; framed, glass, BW. Jane Stanford ca. 1900. frame 38x30 cm, image 19x14 cm. [REMOVED 2/2006], ARCH-AM-2000-271 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, Football players of 1890's. 36x180cm., ARCH-AM-2000-330 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, framed glass. 3 7X47 cm. BW photo, 22X17 cm; David Starr Jordan as old man with sheep dog and monkey., ARCH-AM-2000-167 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, framed, BW, glass, Class of 1899 reunion, (15th) of 1915 at McDowell home on campus. Some identified; frame 26x43, image 24x41 cm. [REMOVED 2/2006], ARCH-AM-2000-277 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, framed, glass- Quad, oblique front viw, pre-1906. Frame 13x31 cm. Image 8x26 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-264 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, framed, glass, Memorial Church pre 1906, front view, BW. frame 41x33 cm, image 34x26 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-276 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, framed, of Edgar F. Smith, provost, 1925 [frame 48x58 cm; photo 38x50 cm], ARCH-AM-2000-152 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, Framed. 33X36 cm. BW shot of Benjamin Harrison, Leland Stanford and John Wanamaker., ARCH-AM-2000-173 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, Framed. 52X42 cm. BW photo: 33X25; Stage of first Assembly hall., ARCH-AM-2000-163 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, Framed. 52X45 cm. BW photo33X24 cm. View of stage of assembly hall., ARCH-AM-2000-164 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, Framed. 52X45 cm. glass. BW photo, 33X20 cm. Early Assembly Hall. View of Organ pipes., ARCH-AM-2000-162 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, Framed. 53X60 cm. BW photo 37X28 cm of Rhodes Scholars at Oxford, 1903., ARCH-AM-2000-159 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, Framed. 59X70 cm with glass tinted photo of Jane Stanford, 26X39cm. Purple and gold matting., ARCH-AM-2000-165 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, Leland Stanford Sr. and Jane. 14x9 cm. (two. In double picture frame. elaborate gold frame, doors cover photo.), ARCH-AM-2000-117 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, man with beard, 33x33 cm. photo, 44x44 cm. framed under glass. Initials "G.T.T." on photo., ARCH-AM-2000-112 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, sepia, framed, glass; Musical group, men students in tuxedos with instruments, early 1900's. frame 48x58 cm, image 32x42 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-307 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, sophomore tie-up, 1921, 20x69 cm. BW framed under glass. Tie-up, Oct. 3, 1921, Freshman vs. Sophomore; Participants massed on playing field, ARCH-AM-2000-111 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, Stanford Baseball Team, 1922, 16x64 cm., framed under glass, "Stanford vs. Braves", ARCH-AM-2000-110 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, Stanford Baseball Team, 1922; 16x64 cm., framed under glass, BW, in Honolulu with Honolulu team, ARCH-AM-2000-109 (Box 1)
  - Photograph, Stanford Quad /?pre 1906, 25x43 cm.; 37x56 cm. frame. Front view of memorial gate and Quad., ARCH-AM-2000-114 (Box 1)
  - Photograph; BW, on Stretcher; Vina Ranch-- dwelling at Headquarters. 64x76 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-321 (Box 1)
  - Photograph; framed, 2 tennis players. Sis Larkin. Photo by Hans Roth. c. 1940's. frame 50x40cm, image 26x33 cm. UNFRAMED AND ADDED TO OVERSIZE GP IMAGES, ARCH-AM-2000-325 (Box 1)
  - Photograph; framed, BW, Quad and Hoover Tower, Aerial view. frame 64x72cm, image 44x55 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-283 (Box 1)
  - Photograph; framed, BW. Dr. B.C. Blodgirl. Univ. organist; 1904-1907, frame 43x29 cm, image 26x15 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-270 (Box 1)
  - Photograph; framed, glass, BW sepia. Jane Stanford, standing, 3/4 portrait. frame 53x35 cm, image 53 x 34., ARCH-AM-2000-285 (Box 1)
  - Photograph; framed, glass, BW, oval matt. David Jacks (1822-1909). frame 62x50 cm, image 45x34 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-304 (Box 1)
  - Photograph; framed, glass, BW; Dr. J.M. Matyke (Faculty). frame 61x42, image 26x32 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-308 (Box 1)
  - Photograph; framed, glass, BW; faculty on Quad. 1914. image 16x85 cm., ARCH-AM-2000-292 (Box 1)
  - Photograph; framed, glass, BW; faculty on Quad. 1914. image 16x85cm., ARCH-AM-2000-293 (Box 1)